

CONTACT

- +593998651891
- luiseducol13@gmail.com
- https://the-lu.vercel.app/

SKILLS

- Designer web
- Nextis
- Svelte
- Creativity
- persistent
- Good leader
- Designer ux/ui
- Problem solving

LANGUAGE

- Spanish Native
- English A2

LUISANGEL TAPIA

Full stac Developer

Junior programmer hungry for success, hard working and always trying to find the most innovative way possible, always taking each task or project to its maximum expression. In fact, a junior programmer with few experiences but with great expectations about the technological world.

EDUCATION

2022- 2023 Full Stack Devoloper. Academlo.

2012-2020 Medium Technician in Machine and Tools. E.T.I "Joaquin Avellan"

EXPERIENCE

Worind Guayaquil, Ecuador 2022 Designe web

Worind Guayaquil, Ecuador 2021 - August 2022 Milling Turner , CNC Programmer August

Sincatesa Maracay, Aragua, Venezuela Enero 2020 - Marzo 2020 CNC Programmer

Main projects

Ecommerce ResApi

Create in BACKEND of an ecommers in 5 days

- We developed an Ecommers-API with stylized cart functions using express as a nodejs framework.
- It has user registration for either seller or buyer
- It has a database with PostgreSQL using sequealize as orm.
- Sellers can create products.
- When registering a registration email is sent and when making a purchase as well.

Ecommers Frontend

Create an ecommerce in 7 days with React

- with shopping cart functionalities.
- Registration and login of users.
- Page for each detailed article.
- also includes filtering

Binance Pay Web

Implement Binance's payment method for product sales or ecommerce.

- Made with nextJS.
- without any reference where you can read only the Binance website.
- NextUI Implementation.

Technology

HTML, CSS, JQuery, NodeJS, Express, (NoSQL), Git, Heroku, GitHub, Bootstrap, Sequealize, PostgreSQL, Reactjs, Nextjs, Svelte, Nextui, Paypal, BinancePay.